when y'all get into my comment sections
asking me if I saw what Amanda seal said
or mentioning Amanda
seals I ignore it because nine times out
of 10 I have seen what Amanda seals have
said and I'm ignoring
her why not because she's not educated
and she's not smart we all know that
she's educated and she is an intelligent
black woman
but when Amanda seals came out few
months ago whining that she's she hasn't
been honored she's not invited into
certain spaces d d d da I completely
understand why Amanda seal Amanda seals
has been basically
blackballed from the industry she's not
a likable person and just because she's
loud and forceful in what she says it
does not mean that Amanda seals is
always right so I see a clip is going
viral where Amanda seals is talking
about her lack of support for vice
president K Harris and be clear I don't
care if she supports her or not she's
entitled to do that she's entitled to
her opinion however I have to push back
on any notion that vice president KLA
Harris erases or marginalizes systemic
racism especially as vice president when
there is ample evidence to the contrary
so I'm just going to lay out where
Amanda makes points about things that
need to be addressed and where vice
president K haris stands on that we have
shooters that are going into places and
killing people because of their race and
then we're not calling it domestic
terrorism what we know from the
intelligence Community one of the
greatest threats to our national
security is domestic terrorism
manifested by white supremacists we have
an entire culture of police that are
killing black people and getting away
with it because the law says they can I
was as a senator as a United States
Senator a co-author of the original
George Floyd Justice and policeing
act and as Vice President of the United
States we demand that Congress passed
the George Floyd Justice and policing
act Joe Biden will sign
it and we should not delay and we will
not be denied
it is nonnegotiable we have a country
that was 1,000% built on the foundation
of racism that now legislators are
trying to pretend did it happen and are
getting that through and doing it on an
education level black history is
American
history living history breathing history
history that we create every day and
history that we then must teach and
celebrate a history that helps us to
understand how the past has influenced
the present and potentially our
future and let us all be clear we will
not as a nation build a better future
for us America by trying to erase
America's past and on a Dei level you
cannot as the second in
line to the highest form of office in
this
country make a message on
Hope and so these are issues that we
must confront and it doesn't it does not
help to heal our country to unify us as
a people to ignore the realities of that
so what have we learned if you care
about what the vice president has to say
about certain issues maybe you should
start paying attention to her when she
speaks instead of taking a headline and
running with it but that's reesi I'll
tag her down in the description box so
you guys can follow her with that said
there are other people out there that
are
debunking everything that Amanda seals
has had to say about president
presidential candidate Camala
Harris and as I stated Amanda seals is
intelligent and she is smart so you have
to ask what issue is Amanda Seal's
dealing with that has her coming out and
allowing these blogs to use her to
spread lies on another black woman
just because you're loud and forceful in
what you have to say it doesn't mean
what you're saying is factual or truth